Heat [music]
[music]
up
here.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey family. Hold on. Let me adjust this.
How are you guys? Hold on.
Okay.
This was a last minute decision to do
this live. You guys know that on Mondays
I usually do um lives with Carlos King
at 7 o'clock Eastern Standard Time.
However, with Love Island about to kick
off very shortly. Ooh, I'm so hot.
Where's my little fan? [snorts] Sorry,
guys. I've been running around all day.
I've been working since 6:00 a.m. So, I
am tired. The reason why we were about
60 seconds late, even though I said
we're going to be on time, is because I
had to shove a boiled egg in my mouth
because I haven't eaten anything all
day. I needed some protein. Um, so yes,
usually I do Carlos King at 4:00
Pacific, 7 o'clock Eastern. I'm going to
continue doing that. and
shout out to the blue crew. Um, Love
Island is coming up and so I want to get
into the muscle of doing Monday
quickies. Oh, my hair is looking all
over the place, y'all. I literally just
came out the shower and finished drying
my hair. So, it's still a little wet.
Lord,
[sighs and gasps] and I can't believe
that we're doing this quickie about Dr.
Cheyenne Bryan. I told myself I was not
going to talk about this lady. Um, but
the story just continues to be uh a
teachable moment uh that I have not seen
in quite a while, which honestly is the
only reason I'm covering it. By the way,
guys, I'm not covering this. Hold Hold
on. My little thingy is not stable. And
I have If I'm not stable, this live is
not going to be stable. Here we go. All
right. So, the reason I'm doing this,
you guys know I am not an ambulance
chaser. I'm not doing this just because
it's viral. I'm doing this because I
think there's value in the conversation
that we can have around what we're
witnessing in real time as far far as
Dr. Bryant. Um, also too, I like the
idea of us doing Monday quickies. That's
going to be our new thing. Shout out to
the Monday quickie crew. So, on Mondays,
we're going to be having quickies from
about maybe 2:30 or 2:15 to about 3:45
when I have to log off to join Carlos.
So, I think this is the perfect thing
for a Monday quickie. Hold on. Is the
fan I need the fan to do its job, honey?
his mother is. Imagine sitting here with
full makeup and wet hair. So, I need
This is not hot flashes. This is just,
you know, trying to I'm diffusing my
hair on camera, y'all. This is how much
this is last minute. So, we're going to
get right into it. Why did I feel like
this was a good teachable moment? P.S.
The show is sponsored by ADHD, so you
know I have to have an ADHD moment.
Remember when we when we were little
kids and we were talking to the fan?
Hello. That doesn't work anymore. Hello,
man. The kids don't know what they're
missing out on.
Somebody said, "Monday cookies is crazy.
It's on brand for me, isn't it, though?"
I want you guys to get used to our
Monday cookies. What's up? Um, so I
was stunned when I last night saw the
clip of Amanda Seals coming to Dr.
Bryant's defense and I said, "Ain't no
way." Amanda and I don't always agree on
everything, but she's a very brilliant
woman. And I always say that brilliance
and integrity are not always friends.
Brilliance and consistency are not
always friends. Brilliance and emotional
intelligence are not always friends. And
I will always acknowledge brilliance
where I see it. Right. Amanda Steals is
brilliant. Full stop. And she has some
views that tend to feel like she moves
the goalpost in ways that stunn me
because I associate her brilliance with
being a little bit more intellectually
consistent. I was stunned when I watched
a clip of Amanda Seals not only caping
for How pretty is this fan though? It's
gold. This is kind of cute. I could put
it on my lapel. Sorry, I feel like I'm
doing QVC. Um, not only was I stunned
that she was defending Dr. Bryant, I was
also further taken aback when she
invoked the name of Maya Angelou. I
almost said Maya [ __ ] Angelou cuz
she's a big deal.
Amanda, I know you have me blocked on
Instagram because I did that video where
I talked about being autistic doesn't
mean that you need to be allergic to
accountability because I'm autistic and
I still say sorry. I know you blocked me
because of that video even though I
stand behind that point and I would die
on that hill. You can be autistic and
apologize. Just saying. So, you have me
blocked on Instagram, but if you happen
to see this girl,
I respect you too much
girl.
You
You invoke the name of Maya an Dr.
MayaAAngelou. Honey, let's suck the
doctor out. You invoke the name of Dr.
MayaAngelou. I I can't even not saying
it because the troll in me wants to keep
on calling her Dr. Myangelou just to be
an [ __ ] baby.
And here's the thing. I'm going to say
something that I didn't think I was
going to say because this is the kind of
point that gets made by low-level
thinkers who are have lazy logic in
comment sections who have no range. So,
I'm always remiss when I have to echo a
sentiment of of someone who is lazy and
has no range. However, a broken clock is
right twice a day. Baby, you keep on
slipping in to your rhetoric that you
think the reason people have an issue
with you is not because you're
insufferable, self-indulgent, and
allergic to accountability, but that
it's because you're light-skinned and
cute. And I can't but help but think all
those times that I intellectually went
at you diminishing everything every
valid critique you ever received to
people just hating light-skinned women.
I'm wondering if that's why you found
yourself doing these mental gymnastics
to in one breath say what she did was
wrong but in the next breath defend her
and mention myangelo.
[snorts] Is Dr. Bryant who you think you
are? Like the way that her pretty
privilege is working for her. Is that
what you were trying to make fetch
happen? And we were like, "No, baby, you
cute and all, but we see you as the
smart one." Oo, Boner. Okay,
let's Sorry, let me let my hair dry and
play the video, child, cuz we This is a
quickie. We only quickie means we got
like 75 minutes. Okay, let for those of
you who are the 40% who come in here,
um, by the way, hi. Let me do the intro.
Hi, my name is Blue Too. I'm a writer,
producer, content creator, emotional
intelligence coach, and all-around bad
[ __ ] who specializes in using pop
culture and politics as a launchpad to
talk about why emotional intelligence is
universally necessary for all parties
involved. Right? Emotional intelligence
is a necessity for everybody. And
there's no better realm than pop culture
to show in real time how necessary it
is. Right? So, we do here what we call
edutainment. We don't just talk to be
talking. There's plenty of other
channels to do that. If you want to kiki
and spill tea, there are plenty of tea
channels. I don't I don't need to buy me
a teapot, right? Although I have a cute
one in my house. Has a little heart on
it. It's very cute. We're here to
elevate. And I am dismayed and stunned
that a mind as brilliant as Amanda Seals
could get it so wrong about something so
simple. Let's see. You all so obsessed
about Cheyenne Bryant. I'm beginning to
think that this is a bot thing.
Why are you so obsessed about this?
Like, okay, she lied. I can see if she
lied and like harmed people.
>> Pause. I can see if she lied and harmed
people. You don't think someone lying
about being a mental health professional
during the biggest mental health crisis
of of our lived lives? Of our lives.
Okay. This life that I'm living right
now, we are in perhaps if not actually
not perhaps, [ __ ] it. It's a fact at
this point. They've done studies. We are
in probably one of the most
gargantuan mental health crisis of
modern history.
And you don't think that while the world
is burning and our minds are collapsing
that someone lying about being a mental
health doctor is harmful.
This let me tell you how how how much I
cognitive dissonance I have about Amanda
being this much of a [ __ ] donkey.
Because again, I don't have to agree
with her to think she's smart and this
is some stupid. This is stupid. I've
never in my life called a man still
stupid. Never.
Never.
This is stupid.
I checked four different sources to make
sure this was an AI.
Now, if there's another AI video in
here, I was too busy checking Amanda's
video, so it might have slipped through
my my clutches. I spent the majority of
my research time trying to disprove this
clip because my brain could not conceive
that on her worst day, she would think
someone lying about being a medical
doctor in mental health during every
type of mental pandemic you can think of
happening concurrently was nonharmful.
And yet here we are.
>> But she was on my podcast and she was
brilliant.
Oh, so because she was on your podcast
and you liked her because she knew how
to stroke your ego. Because people who
are narcissistic, not diagnosing, I'm
I'm naming a trait. You put the IC, it's
not a diagnosis. Fun fact, people who
are narcissistic
often know how to stroke other
narcissistic people. And so, because she
stroked you correctly and you [snorts]
identified her as a fellow pretty
light-skinned girl who gets hated on
just for being pretty and light-skinned,
you think she's nonharmful.
Somebody said, "Amanda, is you cool?"
That That is
We got so much more video to play. I
think you're watching me reexperience
this. Like, I am
I didn't expect our Monday to start off
like this. I didn't expect I had a a
very cute, chill Memorial Day weekend
and and then here comes Amanda. And by
the way, Amanda,
who are your friends? I'm being sincere.
Like, I'm not even trying to be a mean
girl right now. I want to know. I know
you have a lot of male friends, right? I
know that you're friends with
Charlemagne the God, Mark Lamont Hill. I
have J uh James Bland, my friend John
Lee. I I know a lot of people personally
who I adore as men who are your friends.
Who are your girlfriends? I'm going to
ask Amanda Seals this. Do you have any
strong relationships with women who you
consider your intellectual equals who
can hold you accountable without there
being any sort of tension?
I am now wondering that because funny
enough, you just revealed yourself
because like Cheyenne Bryant, Cheyenne
Bryant has female friends who are used
to being attacked and because they're
used to being attacked for being pretty,
they immediately have her back from a
place of kinship. I understand that. I
understand why someone like Claudia
Jordan, my co-host, would be cool with
her because Claudia knows what it's like
to be a brilliant, beautiful woman to be
hated on with lies. And Claudia is very,
very loyal. And I completely understand
why she has her back as a loyal friend,
right? I've been that loyal friend who
years later had to be like, "Oop, I
might have picked the wrong team, but
the integrity of my friendship means I
don't regret having your back until I
knew better." Right? So, I understand
that Claudia being your friend. But for
Amanda,
I think Amanda might fall into the
second category of people who are
friends with people like Cheyenne Bryan
of women who have a similar grift and or
blind spots and so it becomes
Spider-Man.
That is the only way.
That's the only way that intellectually
as brilliant as you are, you said this
dumb [ __ ] on social media.
That's the only way. And by the way,
this might not look like it because I
speak very passionately. This is me
trying to show Amanda Seals's grace.
This is me still not wanting to admit
that she's malicious and she's a grifter
who's covering for another grifter. I'm
trying to think maybe y'all have similar
blind spots. That's the nicest way I
could conceptualize that you said this
[ __ ] But let's continue. Let's
continue.
>> I think it's [ __ ] up that she lied.
Okay.
So, you admit as [ __ ] up that she lied
even though you can't admit that lying
about being a doctor during mental
health crisis is harmful. So, you and
Logic are doing double Dutch. Okay,
you're trying. I'm listening.
You know, and then that's that. The the
the need to
if y'all went this hard against like Kla
Harris.
>> There we have it.
If y'all went this hard, for those of
you who are new here or just haven't
seen every single minute of my content,
I did a live several several several
months ago. I don't talk about Amanda
Seals often. And in that live, I said
that that Amanda Seals has shown to me
at this point, this is an opinion, not a
fact, cuz I know the difference. It is
my opinion
that even though politically she can't
stand Barack and Kamla because you know
radical people who are super radical
can't stand them right so there's
moderate radicals and then there's
radical radicals and a lot of my radical
friends who are third party can't stand
Kamla and Barack Obama with Amanda
though
the way she focused on Kla Harris
instead of Donald Trump when Donald
Trump had already won and was the one
actively causing harm arm. I said, "Now,
baby, this not about the election no
more. He president. Why are you talking
about the candidate who lost while the
one who won is the one who's who's
putting [ __ ] on the walls like just
smearing pool on the walls?" her not be
her the fact that she in 2026 still gets
sexually aroused talking about Kla
Harris and Barack Obama as if they were
president and vice president currently
and has as much eye for them as people
who are sitting down as the [ __ ] who's
sitting in office [ __ ] things up. I
was like, "Oh, this is not about logical
being radical no more. Something's off."
And then it hit me. They get the kind of
approval as shiny light-kinnings that
she doesn't have and she resents them.
I've always said there's very few people
in this world who resent me more than
other women who look like me and who
talk like me. Because it's almost like
if I get favor in a way that they didn't
get if they have a lack mindset, they
think that me having favor is why they
don't have favor. They don't recognize
that we have our own [ __ ] uh paths to
to to traverse despite have being the
same archetype. Amanda has a special
kind of eye for liberal light-skinnings
who are beloved by the same community
that she claims to be shunned by.
That is my personal opinion, not a fact.
Yes. So, the fact that we're talking
about Cheyenne Bryant and 37 seconds in,
you find a way to bring up Kla Harris,
baby, how we get here so fast.
Never once in talking about Cheyenne
Bryant have I ever wondered. Yeah. See,
that's why I don't [ __ ] with Kla Harris.
Never once
ne you guys. Do I have any fruit in my
teeth? Cuz I was eating fruit before.
Listen. Okay. Never once in me thinking
about Cheyenne Bryant and you know I
have ADHD. My brain, if you see me
fluffing my hair, it's because it's
still wet. So I'm trying to make sure
that it doesn't dry limp. For those of
you who don't know about diffusing hair,
child, you got to dry it up so that it
doesn't, you know, drag your face down.
So, I apologize right right now. Oh,
this color is so cute on me. You guys
were right about the ginger, y'all.
Y'all were right about the ginger. I was
trying to go blonde this summer, but
y'all talk me out of it. So, for you to
get to Kla Harris this quick, not only
am I feeling like your blind spots are
very loud, I'm also feeling like you
haven't evolved since the last time I
saw you on social media, cuz I don't see
her on social media much. There's
nothing worse than you going ill.
I don't enjoy this. I'm I'm going to
divest my energies from this. and you
leave somebody because they're on some
weird [ __ ] and then months and months
later you come back and they're exactly
where you left them. I am stunned by the
lack of Amanda Seal's evolution right
now. I'm stunned by her lack of
evolution for supporting a genocide then
like what would that that would matter
to me.
I don't I don't have there's no match. I
don't need to have some type of debate
with Dr. with Cheyenne with Cheyenne
Ryan. At the end of the day, for some
reason, she felt like she needed to lie
about credentials.
>> At the end of the day, for some reason,
she felt like she needed to lie about
credentials. Okay. And at the end of the
day, someone felt like they need to rob
your house. How is that a point?
Uhhuh.
Usually when someone says at the end of
the day, they're about to put a a a bow
on something. I think your bow is loose.
At the end of the day, I felt like Robin
robbing you. And so that's that. It be
that's it. BABY, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
You sound like you you wrote the forward
to Dr. Cheyenne's book because y'all
know I tried to read the first paragraph
and thought I was having an aneurysm
because it was like Dr. Seuss had gotten
drunk on [ __ ] psychedelics.
I'm starting to see the resemblance.
Amanda, I really wish you hadn't done
this because we weren't clocking how how
much we have in common with Dr. Bride
until you did this [ __ ]
>> I don't know why.
>> Mhm.
>> I think part of the reason is because we
live in a a world where we act like
credentials is what determines
somebody's effectiveness.
>> Now, let me say this. I will be fair
because this is not about a dog policies
of intellectual discourse, right?
I am someone who is an emotional
intelligence coach. There's no degree
for that. I know I mentioned that I
learned about emotional intelligence at
a job that I had at the Harvard School
of Public Health. Yes, I worked at
Harvard. I learned about this at
Harvard. I did not go to Harvard for
this as a schooling technique though. I
was an employee of Harvard, right? Big
difference. Unlike Shyen Brian, I don't
need to lie about my credentials. Right?
There are some ways in this world that
you could be heavily influential where
no credentials exist.
I agree. There are ways to be incredibly
effective in a field, in a lane, in a
role where there's no credential. It's
either on you or it's not. You're either
anointed with this calling. You either
have this effectiveness or you don't.
And there's no classroom you can be in
that can teach that to you. I agree.
BEING A THERAPIST IS NOT ONE OF THEM.
That's not where this applies.
BEING A DOCTOR is not one of them.
I
I feel like I'm in the upside down.
I feel like No, I honestly feel like I'm
in the upside down.
I ne I honestly sincerely with all our
disagreements never thought I would see
the day where I would look at Amanda
Seals like she's a little bit stupid.
This is this is actually stunning to me
right now
>> across the board. And in some respects,
it is absolutely necessary. And in her
respect, it actually wasn't necessary
for Wait. And in some So, she's saying
in some respects, it's necessary to have
schooling, but in her respect, it isn't
the respect of being a doctor.
You know when people put their cords
behind the TV and they don't have one of
those cord organizers, so the cords get
all jumbled up and it's just a big old
ball and now every time you tug on the
cord to loosen it, it tightens it
somewhere else and now you have a big
old messy knot. I feel like Amanda is is
is creating a knot of logic. She keeps
on saying things that don't make sense,
but then pulling on the string and
saying things that do make sense and the
bullshit's just turning into a [ __ ]
balloon knot.
>> [sighs]
>> Y'all going out bad for her to do the
work that she does. That being said, I
just don't care.
>> Okay, I don't care.
>> If you don't care, then why are you
making the video?
Y'all don't understand how many times
y'all made me do videos I I don't care
about. Um, and I tell you I'm doing the
video because y'all made me. Um, and I
at least do research because if I'm
going to if I'm going to be apathetic
about something and recognize that
objectively there is some value in me
listening to requests to do it anyways.
There's a little bit more research. But
to say you don't care, do no research,
say blatantly dumb [ __ ] that doesn't
make no [ __ ] sense, THEN SAY A couple
of things that do make sense, and then
reiterate you don't care. Why didn't you
take a nap? It's a three-day holiday.
You're self-employed.
You didn't have to do this. I don't
understand.
She was on my podcast and she was
incredible. I don't care.
incredible. I don't care. For someone
who doesn't believe in capitalism,
Amanda, you and the bottom dollar seem
to be tongue-kissing on this one. So,
because she was good for your bottom
dollar,
you know what? I just had a feeling
right now. What if Amanda Seals is doing
what Melissa Ford does? Whenever Melissa
Ford sees a moment, and Melissa Ford is
my former podcast co-host. You guys know
the story if you haven't. It's on my um
in the members only area, what happened
between us. But whenever something
happens that's influential, Melissa Ford
will go through the crates and post a
clip to remind you that she interviewed
that influential person so that you can
watch that clip back. back when Malcolm
Jamal Warner died, she got a lot of
backlash because people thought it was
tacky that she made it a point to be
like, I'm the one who did the last
interview with Malcolm Jamal Warner
before he died. Now, I'm on the fence
about that cuz I work in digital media.
It is good marketing if someone passes
away who's a legend to show a clip from
you doing their last episode when they
were alive. That actually makes sense. I
am going to be fair to Melissa. That was
good marketing even though it was also
arguably tacky as marketing. Both can
coexist. Yes. I'm starting to wonder is
Amanda's entire point to get us to
realize that her and Dr. Bryant did an
interview so we could go find that
episode of her podcast. Amanda, for
someone who doesn't believe in
capitalism and who thinks that we're all
just bots who are glamored by optics, is
this like a lazy way for you to get some
more revenue, ad revenue on that episode
you did with Dr. Bryant? Because nobody
talked about you and Dr. Bryant doing a
show together. We're all finding out
that you did an episode with Dr. Bryant
by you doing this.
It is giving broke. I don't like to
count people's wallets. I've been rich.
I've been broke. I've been confused.
Somewhere in between. Okay. What goes up
must come down. That's why I have a high
yield savings account. Yes. So, I'm not
the kind of person who enjoys
disparaging people for being broke
because I feel like money is is is very
fleeting. It comes and it goes and you
have to have a good relationship with
yourself even when it's not around. And
however, this is given broke. this given
that Q1 wasn't that great to you and you
trying to make the best of Q2
and as somebody who eats edibles you
might be getting Let me not
Amanda look like she smoked her a good
old something ate her a cute little
edible and said [ __ ] it y'all talk about
Dr. Bryant I talked to Dr. Brian, let me
give me some more clicks.
I'm not mad at it. I'm just wincing at
it. Okay. I'm not mad, just wincing. Not
judging, just perceiving. Yes. Oh, [ __ ]
People are going out bad. I think it
sucks. And I think it was not smart. And
I think that at the end of the day,
there are people who work really hard to
get doctorates. There are also people
who call themselves doctor when they get
an honorary doctorate. And I don't think
that's much different.
>> Huh.
Wait,
what do you mean you don't think it's
different? It's very different. It's
apples and and and and tires. What do
you mean it's that different? It's very
different.
>> I don't think it's much different.
Maya Angelou was walking around calling
herself Dr. Maya Angelou. She didn't
complete a doctorate.
>> [ __ ] Okay,
I know I've already seen this clip, but
now I'm I have fresh rage. I know
there's no way in [ __ ] hell that you
just compare Dr. Cheyenne Bryant to Maya
Angelou.
Amanda Seals, you are one of the most
brilliant minds of our generation. I'm
not glazing you. I'm being honest that I
think you are absolutely brilliant. This
is easily the dumbest [ __ ] that I've
seen you say in a very long time. And I
think it might also be a recession
indicator. Amanda Seals
telling people that lying about being a
therapist during the greatest mental
health decline of our generation is not
harmful.
And then flippantly saying, "Well, she
was on my show. Go watch it. She was on
my show and she was brilliant, so I
don't care. And if Dr. Maya Angelo could
be a doctor, why can't Dr. Cheyenne
Bryant?" Baby, this is a recession
indicator. Okay. The tax man is knocking
on your door. You know what, baby? You
know what? Because I understand what
it's like to need money. If this is how
you got to pay your mortgage, I almost
feel like I should let let you have
this. I cannot take This is satire. This
feels like someone who hates Amanda
Seals is cosplaying as Amanda Seals via
deep fake. You're too brilliant for this
[ __ ] Amanda.
Child, let me let me take a sip of
something. We just started and I'm
already getting pissed.
The intellectual dishonesty
in this live, in this clip is stunning
to me. It's absolutely stunning. Wow.
Some university gave her a doctorate.
Which university was it? Was it
Spellelman? I think it was Spellelman.
It's like faux faux rage to be like all
up in arms about this one person.
One person who's on a tour and being
heavily platformed to millions and
giving harmful advice that centers the
male gaze while weaponizing
uh therapy speak that she's misusing
under the guise of being a licensed
professional until she was caught.
You think that's full rage? Oh, baby.
Uh, meanwhile, me. Okay, so Dr. Bryant
lying about being a doctor is for rage,
but you crying outside of a industry
party that you were told you were not
allowed to come into and knew you were
not invited to, and spending weeks in
the news cycle, crying about not going
to a party you were not invited to.
That's not full rage.
You can weep that your castmates found
you insufferable and didn't invite you
to a party, and when you showed up and
did not respect that boundary, they
meant that [ __ ] and still didn't let you
in. You can weep about that and that's
real rage. But someone causing harm as a
public figure while the world is burning
is full rage. Got it, Amanda. You got
it, baby.
You and Logic have clearly been divorced
from each other. Okay. And you've lost
me in the separation cuz what the [ __ ]
Not necessarily. We got a whole lot of
folks claiming to be things. But so
we're going to now talk about the truth
as opposed to what the [ __ ] Amanda just
said. And we're gonna talk about there
are people now coming forward who were
former clients of Dr. Bryant who talk
about the harm that she caused them.
Oh no, look harm. It's almost like being
a doctor but not being a doctor and
charging people $300 to not be a doctor
and saying wild [ __ ] as a non-d doctor
could be harmful if they're suicidal or
in a place of emotional duress.
It's almost if you like you shouldn't
lie about being a therapist because it
could cause harm.
Look at that. Crazy how that works,
right? But when you are charging people
and you have folks in very just
listen, mental health is a a a huge
thing in the black community, right? We
have so many people dealing with so many
past traumas, just just struggling to
make it, just struggling to be present.
You don't need nobody playing in your
face or in your head. But there was a
girl here in Dallas that apparently paid
for one of Cheyenne's sessions. And she
said that she felt more traumatized
afterwards than when she went into it.
>> You hear that? Her patients, Dr. Bryan's
patients are now coming forward and
saying there's a level of care that a
licensed professional is trained to have
and that the the licensing boards hold
them accountable to that because Dr.
Bryant wasn't licensed and has no board
to be held accountable to, the care was
not there and damage was caused.
You guys, I'm gonna say this in a way
that I hope it's going to be more
tactful than how I want to say it.
Stop being in community with people who
do not want to be held accountable.
Community dictates accountability. For
you to be a part of a community, there
has to be a systems of checks and
balances BECAUSE THAT'S THE WHOLE
[ __ ] POINT OF COMMUNITY.
Words mean things. Community is supposed
to be a system of resource sharing,
checks and balances, and growing
together. There's an African proverb
that that goes, "If you want to go fast,
go alone. If you want to go far, go
together." Yes.
The whole [ __ ] point of community is
checks and balances. So, how the hell
are you saying you want to be in
community with us, but can't nobody
check you, boo? Now you Shereé, right?
Now you spring, summer joggers, uh,
fall, whatever. Right? You are she You
are the She by Shereé of therapists.
Actually, no. Shereé, you deserve more
credit than that because them joggers
did come out. You had a fashion show,
but no fashions, but you did actually
have joggers. She does not have a
doctorate, a doctor role. By the way,
Dr. Bryant, you can't even spell the
name of your school. We're going to show
clips later on in this live about how
she she mispronounced the degree that
she lying about.
You not knowing how to pronounce your
own degree should have told somebody
that you didn't have it cuz it's written
on it. Yes.
Then you mispronounced the name of the
school.
Let's continue to laugh. Saying the way
she talked to her made her feel uneasy.
Just a lot of anxiety. It's a lot going
on. So now there are individuals
starting to come forward about their
experiences with Cheyenne. So I want to
make this very clear. I want to thank
everybody for support, but also you have
your naysayers in the background. Me
speaking out is not about me trying to
tear somebody down. It's not looking for
a platform. I want to educate us. And
it's so sad that when we speak up and
talk about This is one of her alleged
former clients. I have to say alleged
because everything has to be
corroborated and I still want to be
responsible, right? I'm not going to be
a hypocrite. This is an alleged former
client talking about how harmed she felt
and how judged she felt. By the way,
guys, I will say this. Dr. Bryant
allegedly caused this young woman harm
because she was judgmental in a way that
a actual therapist should know better.
Should there are harmful licensed
therapists in this world, which again is
why we need checks and balances, right?
The same way there's bad medical
doctors, there's bad lawyers, there's
bad bus drivers, right? Everybody can
suck at their job. The harm that
Cheyenne Bryant caused, had she been
someone who was licensed, this woman
would have had a clear line of recourse
to have some sort of accountability and
retribution because she's just a life
coach with a trademark, right? She's
just a she's a life coach with a doctor
trademark. The doc squad. Shout out to
y'all. I guess this woman now has to
struggle to figure out how to get
justice for what she's alleging because
there is no checks and balances.
I understand being remiss to
champion bureaucratic red tape,
especially now when our government is
basically writing the Constitution on a
napkin. I get it. And though there has
to be a governing board, I I
[clears throat] will say this about
myself.
I recently found a journal entry because
I found an old journal. It's a gorgeous
journal. When I find it, I'm going to
put show it to you guys. In this journal
that I found recently when I went back
to my childhood home, there's an entry
from 1998
where Blue as a young girl was writing
about how I had decided to be a
therapist. Yes, it's no surprise to
anybody. I originally was going to be a
therapist.
Years into my education, I realized I
could not be a therapist because the way
that I wanted to serve was not aligned
with how the oath that the therapists
take. There were certain conversations
that I wanted to have. There are certain
lines that I wanted to push that I could
not do as a therapist. That is why I
decided to be a coach. And though
because I knew I was not going to be
licensed, I had to come up with my own
system of checks and balances. I had to
create my own governing board, right?
I've had friends audit my work. I've
shown what I've done to colleagues. I've
checked in with clients to make sure
that I'm gauging how they're feeling
properly. And and and and when a client
is in a space of duress that is beyond
the scope of coaching, I recommend them
to a licensed therapist.
I check myself all the time. So, I'm not
saying you need a governing board in
order to be effective. I am saying you
need to pay the integrity tax if you
don't have a governing board. The
integrity tax means you have to create
your own checks and balances if you're
going to forgo the ones that have
already been created. Right? You have to
create your own system. And the one
thing that Cheyenne Bryan has shown us
all is can nobody hold her accountable?
Anybody who purports to be helping other
people but cannot be held accountable is
harmful. That is a menace.
Nobody's above reproach. You are a
menace if you think. And here's the
thing, guys. I've said this to so many
people that I have been friends with,
that have been clients of mine. I've
even said this to a couple people that
I've dated. If I can heal you, I can
harm you.
The same doctor who can create like a
new lease on life by giving you a
surgery that changes your life can also
be the same doctor who's super
malpractice because they ruined your
life. If I can heal you, I can harm you.
That's why I always pay the integrity
tax. That's why I'm constantly checking
myself. That's why I make sure the blue
crew and everybody who follows me knows
that. I know we joke about it, but I
give you guys license to be respectful
while you're checking me. I always want
to make sure that the muscle of being
held accountable is not something that's
just coming out of me. It's coming
towards me. That lack of duality is why
this woman is dangerous. This is no
longer funny to me anymore. I was not
going to talk about this topic because I
thought it was messy and annoying and
I'm just going to let it go. Me and
Bridget talked about it on our Patreon.
Like, okay, that's it. I'm not going to
talk about it no more. But now I'm
worried this woman is causing harm.
Now, funny enough, as someone who worked
at the Harvard School of Public Health,
I'm worried this is a public health
issue.
She's a threat to public health. I'm
going to say that on the [ __ ] record.
This is bigger than the Joe Button
podcast and Club Shay Shay and all her
appearances. She is now a threat to
public health. And that is something
that is actually Amanda very worth
taking seriously. Oh, I'm so offended by
that lady. issues that are going on our
community, the people who speak up get
attacked. When you suffer from PTSD and
you had two suicide attempts, you think
I wanted to reach out to her, look for
platforms. You think I wanted to reach
out just for myself? No, I wanted to
help, which is what I have now.
And suffering from a traumatic brain
injury, things look different for me
than everybody else. So, don't please
don't put your experiences on me. But
what I will say, encourage each other
and speak up when things go wrong. Don't
attack people for speaking up. Encourage
people to speak up. You guys be blessed
with this stuff. We have to start taking
care of each other and stop hurting each
other.
>> Dr. Cheyenne Bryant is committing wire
fraud in my opinion.
>> Now, hold on. Now, [laughter]
y'all know I try to have a wide arrange
of viewpoints when we do these lives.
When this lady says she's committed wife
fraud, I said, "Now, hold on, baby."
Now, I said, "What now? What in the
Wendy? Of shouts to Wendy Oo.
Um, what do you mean wire fraud? So,
let's listen to this because this is
probably one of the more unexpected
takes that I've heard about this. Let's
see. Let's see what she has to say.
>> Drop the doctor or provide proof because
what you're doing is wire fraud. And
each instance
is punishable by up to 20 years in
federal prison.
>> Oh.
>> And an instance is not your website.
It's not the one website and that's one
count. Each time a person hires you
because you induced them to by calling
yourself a doctor and a psychology
expert when you are neither of those
things. Each time someone hired you is
account of wire fraud.
>> Boy,
okay, Cheyenne, just tell the people
you're sorry, baby. Girl, I don't want
to see Okay, let's say you made
everything up. Okay. I don't want to see
any black woman in this day and age be
put in jail for an avoidable offense.
Can you please just tell people that
you're sorry and that this was all just
a joke and that you and Nick Cannon and
Cam Newman and Club Shay were running a
social experiment this entire time and
have Juski come down from the sky and
say, "Sych, we're just joking. Please,
I'm begging you, Cheyenne.
If what this lady is saying is true and
that lying about being a doctor and
receiving funds for being a doctor could
arguably be considered wire fraud.
Can Can we have a lawyer check on that?
Can we have a lawyer please check on
that, please? Because that's that's
crazy. And I'm not going to pretend I
know anything about this. I'm just
telling y'all to have a professional.
You see how I know my place? I know my
[ __ ] place. I'm not a lawyer.
Somebody have a lawyer check on that.
>> 20 years each.
>> You cannot pay me to think that she does
not know this. You have to constantly
show that you are who you say you are in
the field that she's in. And there's
also a bunch of holes in her story as to
why she can't show up.
>> You guys are right. That's what Better
Health did and um and people and the
government stepped in. Yes. In fact, I
refused. I was told to have Better
Health as a sponsor and I refused.
Better Health is they're they're the Dr.
Bryant of of mental health apps. So they
are charlatans. If you know any creators
who are shouting out Better Health as a
sponsor, please tell them to cut that
[ __ ] the [ __ ] out.
>> Proof. So, she claims she has a doctor's
in counseling psychology from Argo
University. When you complete a
doctorate, any doctorate, you are
required.
>> Oh, the lady who said it is a lawyer.
Well, [ __ ] There we go. The lady who
said it's wirefra is a lawyer.
Cheyenne, please stop. You're annoying
right now on my feed, but I don't want
you to go to jail, girl. You going to be
somebody's bottom [ __ ] by Tuesday.
>> Hired to write a dissertation. Now, if
you don't know, a dissertation is a
massive research paper. People take
years to finish this, y'all. This is not
no light work, okay? It gets really,
really difficult. A lot of people don't
even finish, okay? This is not anything
to play with. But it gets submitted into
the national public database called
ProQuest. Now, every dissertation from
every accredited university in this
country is in ProQuest, and it is
searchable by anybody. You don't need a
special login. You don't need to pay
anything. You can just go on there, type
in the person's name, and it's supposed
to come up. So, when people went looking
for Cheyenne Bryan's dissertation, they
found nothing. Now, mind you, she didn't
just claim one doctorate degree, y'all.
On Club Shay, she claimed she had three.
So, that means there should be three
dissertations sitting in that public
database, and people can't even find
one. And anyone who actually graduated
from that university can still request
their transcripts.
>> Somebody just asked, "Blue, are you
doing Love Island US and UK?" Um, that's
a good question.
Oh, that's a good question because you
because Maya Jamama
just she's the host of Love Island UK
for the Americans. For those who don't
know, I am an Angle file. I've been
watching British television since I was
7 years old. So, I've been watching Love
Island the UK edition way before the
American one was even conceptualized.
So, I'm an OG Love Island fan. That's a
good question. I'm wondering if I should
do the Love Island UK in the members
wall only. Like, should I do it as a
membersonly offering since it's a more
niche group? I'm I I don't know.
I don't know. That's a good question.
What do y'all think? Members, let me
know. Should we do Love Island UK for
for the members only? Because since it's
more niche.
We'll see. We'll see.
>> The records don't just disappear like
that, y'all, because the school closed.
That's not how that works. That is very
untrue. But let's be real for a second
because forget the transcripts, forget
the records. Let's keep it simple
because this is very simple. If you have
a doctorate, you have a physical piece
of paper that they handed to you that
you take home that lives in your house
or at least your mama house. Okay. So,
where's the actual degree that she took
home? Not only that, they have a
ceremony. You walk across the stage. So,
you mean to tell me she don't have no
pictures of her graduation day?
>> That's true. She went viral several
weeks ago um for wearing a see-through
dress. We had 81 pictures, not 51, 81
pictures of her and the girls night in
Vegas seeing Jeezy in a see-through
dress during a cocktail attire event.
That [ __ ] was on the shape. It was
everywhere. How do we have 80 pictures
of you seeing Jeezy in Vegas, but we
don't have n picture of you getting your
doctoral, your doctorate, [ __ ] I don't
even know what to call it now cuz you
don't know what to call it, right? How
is a woman this attractive and this vain
and this photogenic who loves posting
herself have no pictures of her at
graduation? If I'm going say this right
now, if you have attended any of Dr.
Brian's graduations, please email me at
blu centricadmingmail.com.
We will have you come on the show.
Oh, speak I didn't do any plugs. Um you
guys, the class fall 26. It's going
against the bottom. I always forget to
do the plug. We only have Let's see
before we continue with Dr. Bryant being
a goddamn charlatan and and a in a
public [ __ ] menace at this point. We
have about I think
30% of the tickets left for the fall
class. The fall class is the last class
I'll be teaching for the entire year.
Please do not hit me up by saying,
"Blue, can I take your class?" No. After
fall, we're not we're not doing it again
until uh end of January, top of
February. So, if you're thinking about
joining the class, especially if you are
someone who's on the east coast, who has
an earlier schedule or who international
the Thursday classes still have a couple
of tickets left and and that is fall
26.ventbbright.com.
Once again, fall26.eventbbright.com.
And our very last family town hall,
we're not doing anymore until we're
probably not doing anymore until next
year, honestly. Our very last family
town hall is um going to be on Junth.
Yes, we're having a Juneenth
celebration. And the URL for that I
think is freedom26.eventbre.com.
So freedom226.eventbre.com. The tickets
are like 30 bucks. I mean I don't get 30
bucks cuz you know I have to pay a lot
of taxes on all those tickets. But it's
a very inexpensive ticket. We get
together on Zoom and we talk about the
[ __ ] that I can't talk about on live.
Okay. It's like the members only area on
steroids because I say all the [ __ ] that
I wouldn't even say on members only. So
if you have not joined us for the Junth
yet, we still have tickets available.
Fall sorry freedom26.eventbright.com.
and if you still want to take the class,
it's fall 26. And guys, I am a coach,
not a therapist. And I always say this,
40% of my clients are therapists. And I
love the fact that even therapists,
actual licensed therapists, know that
they still have more to learn. That's
why this [ __ ] is so weird to me. Coaches
and therapists work so well together. We
don't have to lie about being each
other. Such a weird [ __ ] flex, babe.
>> Not a graduation dinner, nothing. Please
go back and listen. She never said
Argusy. She said Argus University.
>> Argus.
>> And so I had to look it up. What the
heck is Argus? Well, once I found it,
Google corrected it to Argusy. And I had
to listen to her over and over and over
and over and over again to realize she
said Argus University. Listen clear
closely. And
>> those asking about better health. By the
way, I think I'm allergic to kiwis, but
I love the green ones at least. Yellow
kiwis are amazing. New life hack. I've
been [ __ ] up yellow kiwis a lot
lately. If you don't like kiwis, but you
like fruit and you want more fiber,
think about trying sunold kiwis. They're
delicious. Um, so the allegations in
broadstrokes, I don't want to be
derailed by this, was basically, and
shout out to Anitra, that they were
charlatans and grifters because they
would have therapists on who didn't
really give a [ __ ] about you, would not
answer you in real time, no sense of
client, patient, like confidentiality
being um, adhered to properly. The way
that they were doing business was shady.
Um, their security, I think, had some
breaches. It was a whole [ __ ] mess.
Imagine if a bunch of licensed
therapists all joined Hinge and
sometimes would respond to you when
they're bored.
That's not the same thing as getting
real help.
And so a lot of influencers who were
championing better health, it's like
when you buy a wig, right? The
influencer who has the wig, that [ __ ] is
luxurious. You get a wig and it looks
like pubic hair stuck to a weft, right?
The product that was being sold to the
influencers was superior to the product
that was being sold to the general
public and they were not being handled
with care. I hope that that helps. And
yes, golden kiwis are [ __ ] delicious.
I'm probably about to [ __ ] them up some
more during this live. I'm so I'm
apologize in advance. But yes, let's
continue to talk about how this lady
don't even know how to say her degree
that she lied about and don't even know
the name of the school.
>> Clearly and carefully. Listen, she said
it so fast. So, no one picked up on it,
but she said Argus University. That's
how you know she lying.
>> So, there's one person who's um
supposedly supposedly suing her um in
civil court because they thought they
were going to go see a therapist and
she's not a therapist. So, I think that
lawsuit is probably on the way. This is
allegedly.
>> And guys, guess who is her most
favorite, sorry, her most famous ongoing
client?
Class, can anybody guess? And those of
you who know, let us know if you know.
Who do you think is Dr. Bryant's
most sorry, Cheyenne Bryant? Who do you
think Cheyen Bryant most high-profile
reoccurring um client?
Ray J.
Ray J is reportedly a long-term client
of Dr. Bryant and we see how that worked
out.
Ray J. Yes, Ray J.
And have we not been talking about how
his mental health has been declining
over the last couple of years?
Have we not said, Ray J, we thought you
almost got it together. What the [ __ ]
happened? Apparently Cheyenne Ryan
happened.
We for someone who says you don't need
to be licensed to be effective, and I
agree cuz I'm unlicensed and effective.
You can't in the next breath say that
your one of your most loyal clients is
Ray J. Your results are not flexing the
way that you are.
But let's continue watching the video.
>> What I heard the other one is that there
was a woman of color who's a veteran who
said that she booked a session with Dr.
Cheyenne Bryant. Went in was told she's
not a high value woman. She wasn't ready
to hear that she's suffering from PTSD.
>> Imagine telling a veteran who's
suffering from PTSD that they're not a
high value woman.
You don't even need a license to know
better. That's just basic [ __ ]
decorum.
>> She left the session very depressed and
in a worse state of mind than she was
before the session. So that's what she
claimed online. Don't know if there's a
lawsuit or not, but I find that
intriguing because hey, like I said
before, she's doing a lot of harm to our
community. We might not be able to see
it right now, but I'm telling you, like
y'all already know, mental health is a
big deal. And our our community has
suffered injustices for decades, for
centuries, and we don't need someone
playing with our minds and manipulating
our minds in any type of negative way.
Um, so also, uh, what else did I hear,
y'all? Um, bear with me. Oh, I'm hearing
that she might not have her masters or
her bachelors. That's what the that's
what the receipts are saying.
>> Now, this is the part that I was like,
now hold on, hold on, hold on.
First of all, let me look up the degree
doctoral
versus doctorate because I was like
maybe there's another degree that we
don't know about.
[snorts] No, there isn't. Hold on.
Not interested. There is no difference
in meaning between doctorate and
doctoral. They simply serve different
grammatical roles. A doctorate is a
noun, the degree itself. So, it's a
doctorate. The degree is a doctorate.
Doctoral is an adjective used to
describe things related to the degree.
But there's no such word as doctoral.
You had two options, a noun and an
adjective. You chose neither.
I'll take what's behind door number
three. Alice, I just make up my own
[ __ ] Vowels for you. You get a vowel.
You get a vowel.
So, you took
the Y off of a ghosty
because you didn't want to finish that
word and you gave that to doctorate and
doctoral and slipped it in there
instead. You just moving stuff around.
You so innovative, girl. You are so
>> Someone in her bachelor's program said
that, "Hey, I saw her in class. I used
to see her around and all that, but I
don't remember her ever graduating." And
we are a small class, a small community
because her emphasis was in Panaffrican
studies. And it's
>> Panaffrican studies means she might
really sincerely be the female Dr. Umar.
>> A very small group, small group of
professors, small group of students. And
I know that for a fact because when I
was at Metro State, my emphasis was in
African-American studies. And I know my
my I had Dr. White and I had Dr. Benson.
So we had two main professors and we
knew each other. We knew our different
we knew other students. It was a very
small community. Um, so yeah, people are
saying that yeah, we knew her, but she
never finished this program. We didn't
see her actually walk and finish. So,
she might not even have her bachelors,
y'all. That's crazy to me. Hi.
>> By the way, guys, I think I found her
PhD.
>> It's me, Dr. Cheyenne Bryan's PhD
degree. And I am putting myself at risk
even being here, but I'm here to say I'm
sorry to the good doctor.
>> Look y'all, I was like, we leaving here
with something. Okay, I'm determined to
find this lady's PhD at this point cuz
what the [ __ ] because I'm too fast and
too wanted to be found. That's right.
I'm in the federal witness protection
program and I am in danger and that is
the only reason nobody can find me and
my two
>> Oh no, the school opened Gia. He
actually opened the school. Look it up.
So he actually it took him like 51 years
but he opened the school
>> cohorts because as she said she has
three doctorates. I'm only one of them
but we are all on the run and boy are we
fast. You cannot find us. You can't. And
it isn't her fault. And that's why again
I'm here. Dr. Bryant, I am so sorry, but
I'm in danger. If they find me, that's
the end of me. So just take
>> I saw a video of Dr. Umar defending her
that was blatant AI. It was like blatant
AI. Like very blatant AI. So be careful
by saying that because the ones that I
saw were all AI. I saw one video that I
hope was an AI, but I didn't have time
to vet it that where he was saying the
opposite. So just be careful saying that
he was defending her. from me. Dr.
Brian's PhD degree that is in the
federal witness protection program and
therefore cannot be found for my own
physical safety. We are real. We exist.
And there's several more of me where
that came from. We are all on the run.
>> Titles doesn't make someone
[clears throat] a leader. It doesn't at
all.
>> This is Dr. Brian and Melissa Ford, my
former co-host, uh discussing how you
don't need a title or a degree to be
effective. Again, I agree with that
general point. However, if you are
someone who has any sort of intellectual
integrity, you understand that the
application of a valid point matters.
This is not the right application.
>> It doesn't make you brilliant.
>> THE WHOLE TIME IT'S LIKE THE [ __ ] NO.
>> It doesn't breed someone's results. You
have many people Oprah's one, Tyler
Perry's another, who are no EDUCATION
WHATSOEVER.
>> OH, HELL NO. GIRL, [screaming]
NO. GIRL, DID YOU just
Did she just said because Oprah and
Tyler Perry don't have a doctor? Do
doctor doctoral
means that she don't need a doctoral
capital I for I made it up.
Somebody said y'all be nice. Be nice.
Yeah. Um
but that's not how that works.
>> Pass um high school. who know collegiate
education who have done beyond well.
>> Are you done?
Are you done?
>> So, she's saying, y'all know where this
is going. She's saying that because
Oprah and Tyler Perry uh don't have
degrees, she don't need one either. Got
it. Um and that her effectiveness speaks
for itself.
We saw you having a debate with three
men who couldn't debate. One of with one
of which we're not sure is literate.
That's called punching down.
You don't need to be How is it effective
that you were able to tell Nick Canon
the obvious and Cam Newton the obvious
and Shannon Sharp the obvious? Being
able to tell black men who think you're
pretty the obvious without them calling
you names because they think you're
attractive is not being effective in
helping the community. That's you going
viral and helping your bottom dollar.
Let's show
how effective Dr. Cheyenne Bryan is.
Because again, if you are a therapist,
that means you understand uh your
nervous system needs to be regulated.
You understand what it's like to be
deregulated. You understand trauma
responses. You understand the quorum and
tact um a certain level of social
intelligence. You understand
application. You understand uh
implication, right? You understand that
if you're on a platform and you're
stating a personal opinion that other
people are allowed to have their own
personal opinions and you're allowed to
have a disagreement without it being
adversarial or demeaning. Yes. Somewhere
in you getting a doctoral
capital I because I made it up.
Somewhere in between you getting that
doctoral, you made up your own degree
class. Yes. Because I've never heard of
a doctoral before.
There is supposed to be some sort of
training around discipline, social
discipline, because a therapist has to
be a professional listener. Did y'all
hear what I said? As somebody who was
going to be a therapist, decided to be a
coach, and didn't lie about any of it. A
therapist is a professional listener,
which means it's their job to intake
data, process it, and let people speak,
and then give their feedback. They are
trained in this. I have been on dates
with people when they've been like,
"Blue, you doing the therapist thing
because you haven't talked in five
minutes." I'm like, "I'm just actively
listening. I want to make sure I'm
present for you." The fact that what I
do on a date with a [ __ ] I'm not even
sure I like Dr. Doctoral Bryant couldn't
do with Terra. And y'all know I'm not
the biggest Terra fan. I think Ter gets
it wrong more whether he gets it right
lately. He had a legacy in the um 90s
and early 2000s that was amazing. It has
now been diminished by some of his his
troubling rhetoric. He also replaced me
at the go. So, I'm not even going to
lie. There's some personal grievance
there. When I left the go, he got my
check and did not get my [ __ ] clicks.
Did not go viral the way I did. I'm just
going to say that. Bad investment, huh?
Funny, huh? I'm still viral. He's
whatever. Anyways, I'm not the biggest
Terra fan, right? For professional and
personal reasons. And though, however,
girl, you basically called this man a
[ __ ]
after you interrupted him. Let's watch
the clip. I know you guys have all seen
it by now.
>> Are you done?
>> Only externally, but internally what
they
>> the conversation for those who are the
40% who don't know what's happening
because we always say 60% of you know
what's happening. 40% just come here for
the vibes and to learn. Dr. Bryant is on
a panel with Té and two other panelists.
It's an ongoing show. It's not an
appearance. I' I've heard that this is
an ongoing show that they had. And in
the show, they're discussing corporal
punishment and should you whoop your
kids? And Terra is saying, "I don't
think in this day and age you need to
spank children." And Dr. Brian's like,
"No, whoop that trick. Whoop their ass.
Whoop their ass." And Terra's like,
"Well, I don't think gentle parenting
sucks if you do it correctly because we
could use more gentle men." Like men in
particular have not done well. Black men
in particular have not done well from
getting their ass beat by their mammies
and their papies and they're emotionally
stunted. Maybe being gentler with them
as young boys will help them be more
emotionally INTELLIGENT MEN. DOOR Bryant
responds by, "That's some bullshit." And
I could tell cuz you a little [ __ ]
yourself that you a gentle man. Like it
went left. So, and when he said, "YO,
YO, YO, why are you interrupting me? I'm
trying to close the show." She said,
"Watch your [ __ ] mouth." I I I think
she wanted to call him the N word. I
think she called him everything but the
n-word. Let's just Let's just watch the
clip. Let's just watch the clip. do
carry at the nucleus of who they are is
discipline and boundaries.
>> If gentle parenting creates gentle
children, sign me up. I definitely want
to create more gentle adults.
Especially,
>> by the way, the association like every
association that that stands behind
licensed therapists have the complete
opposite view of what she's advocating
for. I know therapists who might
personally tap their children on the bum
who would never because there's checks
and balances publicly say this. This is
a perfect example of what happens when
there is no governing board.
>> Men, hold on. Especially men.
>> My god. [laughter]
>> Hold on, guys. Hold on, guys. That's
Hold on, guys. Hold on, guys. That's
what we need in the world.
>> Do you see how she spoke uninterrupted
and when he tried to give a
counterpoint, she immediately started
interrupting him and saying, "Well,
you're a very gentle man." So, of
course, she would take that. You see how
she's not even letting him speak? A
therapist is a professional listener.
If you won't listen to a equal, and to
be honest, I'm being kind by calling him
your equal because as far as the social
zeitge guys goes, Terra is has much more
clout than you do, right? If you're
listening to an equal on a panel and
can't even stop to let him finish a
counter point, what are you doing
privately with people who have P PTSD or
complex PTSD or who have some sort of
anxiety disorder who are opening up to
you about their feelings? If you can't
even bring your hubris down to listen to
a fellow panelist with financial and
social incentive to shut the [ __ ] up.
You have financial and social incentive
to shut the [ __ ] up and you still about
to call this man a [ __ ] on on camera.
What are you doing with people who are
not your equal socially and who are in
dire straits needing compassionate care?
This is why this [ __ ] is harmful. is
more gentle men who understand.
>> Hey, you're very gentle and it comes
at an angle that doesn't always work for
for for people.
>> Stop. Let's just stop. Let's just stop.
Let's just stop. Let's just stop and go
back. I'm wrapping the show and you're
interrupting me.
>> First of all,
>> we we spent a whole meeting on this last
ter. Why would you let me wrap the show?
I'm ending the show. What is the point
of interrupting me? First of all, we're
getting out of here. Like, what is the
point?
It says lower voice when you're talking
to me.
>> Lower your [ __ ] voice.
>> Lower your [ __ ] voice when you're
talking to me.
The man said, "Hold on. You see me
reading the cue for us to wrap up. Why
are you trying to argue with me when all
of us know that I'm wrapping up the
show?"
And her response to him making a valid
point is, "Lower your [ __ ] voice when
you talking to me, my nigga."
Amanda, is this the nonharmful?
Is the nonharmful in the room with us?
Is the not causing harm in the room with
us?
>> Talking to me because you're acting
very, very gentle, very soft, and very
feminine. And this said,
>> you're acting very gentle, very soft,
and very feminine. What do you think
happens when a couple comes to her and
the man is grappling to be open with his
wife about his his feelings and his fear
of intimacy because he doesn't want to
be called a [ __ ] knowing that his
therapist will call you a [ __ ] on
camera.
Mind you, I don't even like Té and I'm
on his side right now.
>> You talk to your wife like that. You
don't talk to me like that. That is not
how you professionally approach me.
Don't [ __ ] talk.
>> That's not how you professional approach
me. Don't [ __ ] talk to me. How do you
say that's not how you professionally
approach me and then say, "Don't [ __ ]
talk to me like that right afterwards."
And don't see the deep irony in that.
This [ __ ] is satire. This is an SNL
skit. This is She's her own SNL cannot
do a skit of her because she's her own
walking SNL skit.
>> Talk to me like that. Check the [ __ ] up
talking to me like that.
>> I know Trey from the heady days of '90s
hiphop journalism, and he was always a
pretty astute dude. So it shocks me that
he allowed himself to be surprised at
bringing in Cheyenne Bryant expecting
Dr. Jackekal. Yeah, Mrs. Hog may just
show up and that's who that's who did.
But let's say I do realize it and you're
licensed. You're saying I can call
somebody.
>> Oh yeah,
>> but if you're not.
>> So Mark Lamont Hill, I wanted to make a
point because the last time that I
talked about Dr. Brian and Broadstrokes
during our Friday Night Live, you guys
mentioned that this interview had
happened. I wanted to listen to y'all
cuz I'm not above reproach. I wanted to
listen to you guys and and watch the
clip and watch all the clips and see
what they spoke about. It was a great
conversation. You guys were right. Dr.
um Martin was uh a little bit more open
to the value of being a coach in this
discourse than she was in some of those
clips that I found off-putting on her p
her social media page. So, yay for that,
Dr. Martin. And I love that you could do
that because again, an intellectual has
the ability to course correct when they
misstep and get new information. Yes,
that's a true intellectual, not a
doctoral part eye. Yes. So, let's watch
this little clip of their conversation.
>> I can't call anybody. That feels LIKE
>> THAT FEELS LIKE OUT. It's like if I were
a restaurant owner and I decide I don't
I'm not with the Better Business Bure.
It's like like I'm not with the health
department. Like,
>> don't you have to sign up with these
people?
>> Not if you're No. If you're licensed,
yes, that's part of like who you're
licensed with. But if you're say you're
a coach there, you can decide to like
there are some ways that you can be
certified, but you don't have to like
you anyone can state that they're a
coach. Anyone can't state that you're a
licensed mental health professional.
>> I get it. So if I'm a a mental health
professional, I have to be licensed. I
can't opt out. But if I use the word
life coach, I can or career coach or
relationship coach, whatever.
>> That that's the workaround. The
workaround is just saying you're not
that thing. You give it name something
else.
>> Yeah. There's no regulatory body on
coaching. people can take the take the
um there are like certain ways that you
get it's not certified but like there's
like the international coaching
federation and there's a national board
of health by the way I looked into
getting a coaching certificate and
everything that they were teaching was
way like I was about 10 12 years into my
career and I said oh I wonder if I could
get a coaching certificate just so I
could get me a cute piece of paper and
[snorts] quantify and they were like
you're above what we teach this is not a
flexor me being Dr. Bryant, what they
teach in coaching um to be certified is
better suited for newer or intermediate
coaches. I was so deep into my career by
the time I even looked into it, there
was no value because there was nothing I
could learn. I would have been doing it
just for the piece of paper. And mind
you, there's nothing wrong with that. If
I was somebody who thought a coaching
certificate would make me feel better,
sure, but I actually like to learn. I
was like, I'm not paying you off for a
piece of paper. I'm not learning [ __ ]
So, they didn't have anything to teach
me that I found valuable that I had not
already learned. In fact, a lot of times
when people who have been doing the kind
of work that I do for 20 plus years go
back to school, they will give you
credits for time served in the field.
That's the irony. Dr. Bryant says that
she's been doing this allegedly for 17
years.
Okay. While also running for mayor, let
me not judge. If she really had been
doing this for 17 years and could prove
her effectiveness in the community, she
could actually get her doctoral with an
I and have some credits already put
towards that because of time served in
the field. That's what's killing me is
if you really are who you say you are,
it would not be difficult for you to
actually become a licensed therapist
again unless you just never had it.
>> Health and wellness and coaching, you
can decide to go through that like
credentiing ecosystem, but it's
voluntary. Um you
>> for those who are talking about running
for marriage, we will be getting into
that.
>> You can just decide that like oh I'm
really good at problem solving. I
problem solve my problems. I problem
solve my husband's problems. My
>> you know I often tell you guys that on
the internet you could be the butcher,
the baker, the candlestick maker. You
could be whatever you want if you're
charismatic enough uh to draw an
audience. Man, the internet is so is so
uh uh easy today for certain people. You
don't even have to show your face to
make a little to make a lot of money.
And if you look like something, if you
got a pretty face, uh, you show a little
bit of boob, uh, wear a short skirt or
show some legs, oh man, you become an
internet sensation.
>> Yeah. She also claimed that she was
trying to be a law professor. How are
you going to be a law professor? When
did you become a lawyer?
>> Overnight, you'll have a whole bunch of
men and women donating money to you,
mesmerized by your beauty, listening to
whatever you got to say. That's just
what the internet has turned into. They
don't care about the information as long
as you sound good or look good, right?
or give a perception, right? Or give a
perception that they can that they can
envision. Or
>> by the way, guys, I mentioned Oh, that
that cute was so good. I mentioned um
last week that I don't think it's just
pretty privilege that's working in her
favor. I think it's prosperity
privilege.
To his point, right now when everybody
is struggling, anybody whether they're
pretty or not, conventionally attractive
or not, anyone who has the perception
that they have figured out anything
right now and who is not struggling is
going to have some sort of privilege and
be seen as a potential guru because
nobody can figure out anything. Anybody
who can figure out anything immediately
has a opportunity to potentially be seen
as a taste maker or a professional or an
expert in a field that they're not
suited for. Just be really really really
careful that social media has opened up
our minds as far as educating us about
things that we would never would have
known about otherwise. It's also made a
lot of us slaves to optics
>> dream about man you become rich.
>> You know what the real problem is? One
of
>> now Judge Brown
y'all know Judge Brown is problematic.
So I'm about to warn you right now that
what he's about to say is deeply [ __ ]
offensive. But what he's about to say is
so easy to disprove. I wanted him to
have time to cook so I could right after
that uh do a fact check on what he's
saying.
>> One of them is drop dead gorgeous and
the other one's ugly and she really
needs to ditch those white glasses. She
>> He said the problem is one of them is
drop dead gorgeous and the other one is
[ __ ] ugly and needs to get rid of
those white glasses. That is Judge Joe's
professional opinion as a judge.
Raquel Martin is not ugly.
She's not conventionally attractive
because that's a very myopic lens on
beauty, but she's not ugly. That's
[ __ ] up.
>> Looks like a space cadet. But anyway,
bottom line is I've known Dr. Bride for
a very long time. She got an undergrad
degree at 19 years old. She quickly
wound up getting a master's and PhD in
psychology. She was licensed at one
time. She surrendered the license
because a lot of what she did was
controversial. She
>> mind you he's reading off a resume that
she told him.
Whenever y'all speak from a place of
authority or rely on asking yourself who
am I citing as a source? Of course she
told you all that. And can we just check
this for a second? The fact that a black
man who is in a position of power as a
public figure who has millions of people
who know his name is using his platform
and his social currency to disparage the
appearance of your opponent tells me
everything about how crazy y'all are
talking about Dr. Martin behind her
back.
This being your homeboy. If he's talking
about her like this and feels
comfortable like I can just imagine the
[ __ ] that y'all talk behind people's
back.
>> Ran for Congress, almost got elected.
She
>> ran for Congress and almost got elected.
Ran for Congress.
Thank you. Y'all see why I had no choice
but to come back cuz this is bigger than
what I thought it was.
ran for Congress, almost got elected,
applied to be a law professor, but never
went to law school. And the whole time
you might not even have a [ __ ]
regular ass bachelors.
And there's nothing regular about
bachelors. I'm saying that a bachelor's
is considered the bare minimum to say
you're college educated, right? That
you're a college graduate. So,
the opportunity that there might be a a
world where Dr. Cheyenne Bryant did not
even get her bachelors, but is
purporting to have three of every degree
that's ever been made.
The disparity between the truth and what
she's saying, the gap is such a a wide
chasm. I I fear that the irony is a
licensed therapist might need to at some
point diagnose her. That's the biggest
irony in all of this is that a licensed
therapist, you know, the one that went
to our our go with the Y at the end and
not the one that she made up, might
actually need to diagnose her someday.
>> She runs one of the few effective NAACP
chapters in America that isn't off into
that stuck on stupid thing. She also set
up a thing with the LA Unified School
District that deals with the assessment
of race in the
>> [clears throat]
>> uh
school system. She set up a thing with
Los Angeles Police Department where she
was evaluating
the police officers uh on a regular
basis to determine their fitness to
continue to be armed in public.
>> Two black people running. So, this is
the clip, guys. For those who are like,
"Well, when did she say that?" She Oh,
that was a kiwi burp, but it was
delightful because kiwi yellow kiwis are
delightful. Oh, not me having a cute
burp. Sorry. Um, this is the clip of Dr.
Cheyenne Bryant, alleged Dr. Cheyenne
Bryant, explaining to her panelists how
she allowed Karen Bass to win
by recusing herself from the race in
California. because she did not want to
to to divest the vote and take votes
away from her. So the only reason that
Karen Bass is an elected official is
because Dr. Cheyenne Bryant decided to
recuse herself. Oh, how nice of you.
>> Because I did this with Los Angeles. I
was running for LA mayor and then I seen
our mayor Karen Bass come in as a
candidate and she was running against a
a a white male, a Republican and it was
it was neck to neck and I knew that had
I stayed in the race neither one of us
would have ran because two black people
would split the vote. So what I'm saying
right so what I'm saying is I pulled out
so that Karen could win and she barely
won like a needle. Had I even took 200
of her votes then she wouldn't have won.
So I think that Cornell needs to pull
back if we want Kamla to win because
he's going to take her votes. He's still
black. So
>> 12. That's how many people actually
qualify for the 2022 LA mayoral ballot.
This is a fact check, guys, because
unlike Dr. Cheyenne Bryant, I live in a
world where I would like to sleep at
night and not worry that a simple Google
search could show that I'm full of [ __ ]
And you see how I can be effective doing
that without a doctoral.
You see, you see how you don't have to
lie about the irony is that speech she
made talking to Melissa is the point of
contention that many of us have is
you're right. You didn't have to lie
about being a doctor to be effective. So
why are we here?
We agree with you, [ __ ] Now what? Why
are we here?
27 filed paperwork to even try to run.
And Miss Cheyenne Bryant was not one of
them. I'm Tanya Mackenzie, chair of the
LA County Commissioner on Alcohol and
Other Drugs. And chair of the LA County
LA County Commissioner, I need you to
understand who is doing this fact check.
There was a group of 12 and a group of
27. Cheyenne Bryant was in neither
group.
In neither group. Okay, let's listen. I
keep getting asked if Miss Cheyenne
Bryant ran for mayor of LA. And the
answer is no.
She campaigned,
but there's a difference. Let me
explain. There was a website. It's
actually still up. There was a banner.
There was a Dr. for Cheyenne Bryant for
LA mayor 2022 branding. Um there was
some community events, photo ops, the
whole production. What there wasn't was
a nomination papers filed.
>> So wait a minute, let me get this
straight. She got the t-shirts and the
trademark and the website and the
outfits, but didn't actually file any
paperwork.
>> Y'all seen a pattern or no?
Cheyenne Bryant got Cheyenne Bryant for
Mayor 2022 t-shirts and a website and
campaign bumper stickers
but didn't actually file to run just the
optics beautiful gowns.
Y'all not seeing a pattern
in the same way she filed a trademark
for Dr. Bryant, but just didn't bother
to become a doctor first.
It's almost like a leopard doesn't
change its spots. It just changes its
lace front. It's almost like she's a
grifter who's going to keep on grifting
because she cute and we think it's funny
until her former patients who have
complex PTSD, who are former veterans
who came to her with suicidal ideiation,
are now tearfully sharing that she
caused them harm because she didn't have
the training to handle them with care.
And they're being told to shut the [ __ ]
up because they're just haters. Because
she's pretty and they're not. Y'all
don't see the harm in this. You don't
see the harm in that, Amanda?
Uh, there was no candidate statement
filed. There was nothing sent to the LA
city clerk. Nope.
>> So, there's that. Her name never hit a
ballot.
Uh, she never made a qualified
candidates list. She never showed up on
Ballottopia, Wikipedia, or the LA Times
roundup. None of those things happened.
But the website is still up. You can go
check it out. It still says for LA mayor
2022.
It still reads like a campaign is in
progress 3 years later. And that right
there is why people are in my DMs asking
me if she actually ran for mayor because
in 2026, a Canva graphic and a confident
caption will rewrite history. People
don't fact check things. They just
screenshot and keep it pushing. So, let
me be clear with all of you. Announcing
a run, building a site, and showing up
at a community event is marketing.
Filing with the city clerk is running.
[clears throat] One is a brand and the
other is a ballot. Know the difference,
especially before you put it on
someone's bio.
>> This is how you know she really don't
have a degree, right?
>> So, guys, you know, I had to look it up,
right? You know, I had to. Y'all know I
had to.
[ __ ]
the website is still up. [ __ ] I'm I'm
beside myself.
I'm beside myself.
All brand, no ballot.
All brand, no [ __ ] ballot.
Baby, you paid for a background and some
accompanying bellyage in your hair, but
not a ballot.
YOU GOT YOUR LACE FRONT BELLYAGED, BUT
DIDN'T THINK TO FILE the paperwork to be
on a ballot.
But according to you, in the clip we
just saw, you saw that you was about to
confuse the voters. So that's why you
let Karen Bass have it. You let her have
it.
Baby, come's about to let you have it if
you don't stop. I'm so I'm so nervous
for this lady. When I tell you I don't
mean this lady no harm. I actually want
her to get out of her own way. I am ner
the way this is going to have to come to
a conclusion is going to be tantamount
to Icarus. For all of you who know about
Greek mythology, you know Icarus when he
flew too close to the sun and he melted.
Baby, you flying too close to the sun.
You probably don't even know who the
[ __ ] Icarus is. Let me stop child cuz I
learned about that in school. I'm not
sure you've ever been.
>> Because at this point now it's no longer
about proving your degree to the general
public. Proving your degree to the
naysayers. Now you're not having a
degree is going to cause a problem for
them good white folks.
>> Yep.
>> And what I mean by those good white
folks is your book publisher.
>> By the way, that I I do feel like
Cheyenne Bryant would happen if Joanne
the Scammer wasn't in on the joke and
took that [ __ ] serious. It is giving
almost impressive levels of grifting. I
don't think I've seen anybody be this
audacious in a while.
>> So, here is the gag. In order to keep
them from having to refund money and
their credibility being called into
question or whatever legal liability may
rest on them for publishing the book,
hands down, they are going to put
downward pressure on you to show your
degree. And if you are so in your ego
to the point where you would refuse to
show your degree to your publisher
because you don't want to look like you
gave into the people. We know that's
some [ __ ]
>> Yeah. See, now that your money about to
get oper compromised and you won't show
your degree, that's further proof that
you won't have one. Additionally,
>> additionally,
>> oh, there we go.
>> All of those certificates that you got
on that wall behind you
>> Mhm.
>> are indicative of the fact that you were
normal just like the rest of us and you
love to show off your accolades. Yep.
>> Why you agreeing that there
>> squad? [singing]
And we are already on the freaking
bestellers list,
>> you guys. I looked there. I I did not
see a bestsellers list. What list, baby?
It wasn't the New York Times. It wasn't
Good Readads.
Was it Amazon?
So, Dr. Bryant in the middle of all this
is claiming Sorry, Cheyenne girl. Shy.
Shy. Yeah, Sha is claiming that she's on
the bestsellers list. But here's what's
happening in the real life cuz we know
that she has her own version of reality.
>> So, they are pulling Dr. Cheyenne
Bryant's books and they are refunding
people's money for buying those books.
And now, I think it's gotten to the
point where if she truly does have all
the She says she has six degrees, three
doctorates. If you have at least one
doctorate, you need to show your
credentials right now, girl. It's the
time.
>> I believe that Dr. Cheyenne Bryant is
quite possibly the same personality type
as Nick Cannon and Cam Newton. I believe
that all three of you are serial
monogamous with narcissistic tendencies.
First of all, serial monogamy and
narcissism go together. the narcissist
grandiosity too important to commit
one's emotional resources to not want to
invest emotionally. When I look at
>> the reason why I have Dr. Omar talking
is because Dr. Cheyenne Bryant that
whole archetype panders to manosphere
black men prideful black men and she
panders to them in a way that is like
covert pickmeism and she centers their
gays a lot. G A Z gaze, right? So,
because she centers the black male gays
and she at least started to go to school
for pan-African studies, this is exactly
the kind of person who calling her out
might [ __ ] with her brain a little bit.
Right? When you are dealing with
somebody who actually is narcissistic or
a narcissist, but I can't diagnose,
that's why I'm saying ick because the IC
makes it a character trait, not a
diagnosis. Um, narcissistic people
sometimes experience something called
narcissistic collapse where [ __ ] gets
too real. They're paying. They're pushed
in a corner so far that even they have
to call [ __ ] on themselves. If there
was anybody who might help her call
[ __ ] on herself, it would be black
men divesting from her because they're
her core audience.
>> That a woman that beautiful without a
child. The marriage I can understand is
slim pickings for sisters. That
beautiful without a child. Uh-uh. That
was deliberate. And I believe that she
may be an example of one of our sisters
who says they're waiting for the right
one, but may not necessarily be waiting
for anyone at all. But because it's
expected of me as a black woman to get
married, I need to have a justification
for why I am not. I thought I was done
talking about this Dr. Cheyenne exam.
And
>> so, for the sake of time, we're going to
have to skip these and go to the very
end cuz it's 40 past the hour. Jasmine
had an I had a response from Jasmine's
Garden. I'm going to end with Jasmine's
response. But before Jasmine has a I'm
going to let Jasmine have a response.
Then I'm going to show you what do Dr.
Brian had to say to all of us. Some of
you have already said
>> 7:53 this morning before I could have my
first joint and I said unfortunately God
I'm going to share my thoughts with the
people today. [laughter]
>> What is it that Amanda Seals and Madam
Fraud fakey fufu boo last name the
[ __ ] fool Cheyenne Bryant haven't
called me well.
>> Okay, first of all guys I have not seen
this so we're all watching this
together. I literally just grabbed this
clip as I was sitting down. So, we about
to
we about to watch this together. Okay,
let's go.
>> Amanda Seals is self diagnosed and
Cheyenne Bryant is self-decorated in a
bunch of doctoral degrees that do not
exist. So, off bat, we have unregulated
and unqualified women buying into the
same type of bypassing hyping each other
up like, "Yes, bitch." My issue with
you, Amanda, is that you are
intelligent. You have multiple degrees.
Up until this morning, we were still
mutuals because I followed you four to 5
years ago because I appreciated the way
in which you approached conversations.
Even through your frustration and
exhaustion from being frustrated, you
approached conversations that I felt
were very hard to talk about even if I
didn't always agree with the angle that
you came from. I appreciated that you
held room and space for the conversation
to be had.
>> Do you see how so many of us extend so
much grace to Amanda Seals that she will
never admit has been extended?
She's convinced that black women,
particularly dark-kinned black women,
just have a unilateral hatred of her.
When whenever you listen to any
intellectual black woman of a certain
hue, talk about Amanda, you see how hard
they are working to stay in community
with her, even while she's not trying to
be in community with us.
Just want to point that out because I
haven't seen Jasmine's response, but
it's not lost on me that she's going
through the same process that you
watched me go through at the beginning
of this live. The issue now is that you
won't heal whatever this bitter wound
is. This wound that makes you think
everybody has wronged you, nobody
understands you. I've heard you talk
about your pattern recognition so many
[ __ ] times. And I just have this
question. If we sometimes miss social
cues because we're autistic, how do you
always understand what everybody else
[ __ ] means and how everybody else is
intending something to come across, but
everybody else is always
misunderstanding your intention and the
way in which you're coming across. At
what point in our pattern recognition do
we pick up on the pattern that we might
be a [ __ ] At what point in the pattern
recognition do we pick up on the pattern
that maybe we're using our autism as a
mass to disguise the fact that we like
being an [ __ ] sometimes because we
are frustrated and
>> I said the same thing in 2024 and Amanda
Seals blocked me. Oh my god, Jasmine, we
are kindred. I said the same thing in
2024 and I got blocked for it.
>> Exhausted with being intelligent and
having ideas that people don't want to
listen to because maybe it's not the
most intelligent idea in the room. You
grew up in the 80s in Florida going to
school amongst a bunch of white people
and you still have not in your mind
graduated to understanding that you're
in a bigger class called life with more
black people that are in fact smarter
than you. So you don't have all the
answers. I don't think Amanda can
conceive of or even Cheyenne Bryant can
conceive of that some of the people
critiquing them might actually be more
advanced than them in some way.
There's different types of intelligence,
right? Um, perfect example. I have a
very high IQ. I can't read a map, right?
Just because I my IQ is very high and I
have a very strong understanding of
language and and pattern recognition and
numbers there. I still have blind spots,
right? So, you could quite literally
quite literally be tested in the top 5%
of intellect and still have glaring
blind spots and things to learn from
people. And I'm saying that to say there
is no way to quantify that you are this
omnipotent god. Even the smartest [ __ ]
there's somebody smarter than you in the
room. And also, if you're the smartest
[ __ ] in the room, you're in the wrong
room cuz why are you in there? I don't
want to be in a room where I can't learn
[ __ ] I'm bored now. I got ADHD. Why am
I in here?
Gh. People like this who are so
intellectually superior, but
character-wise, um, integrity wise,
social wise, they're stunted. and they
think that one one good thing makes up
for all the places that they fail. They
are frustrating to me because you were
gifted with the hard [ __ ] and yet you're
refusing to do the things that everybody
else has to do. You were gifted with the
hardship. The things that people wish
they had, you were born with. God gave
that to you. But the regular mundane
things that create community are the
very things that you are resistant to.
That is just hubris. That is not autism.
Sorry, I got mad. And sometimes your
approach is in fact wrong. So that day I
was scrolling and I saw you on live and
I heard you come out of your own mouth
and say that you weren't going to pay to
get diagnosed with autism because you
know and that's all that matters. Now I
realized you are scared to sit in the
chair of somebody that's [ __ ]
qualified because you don't want to find
out that people may have been right
about you. Not as a whole but based off
situation and circumstance. But are they
right about you if you keep reinforcing
the thing that they were calling you out
for? If you are so healed because you
said on Shannon Sharp that you know
you've been toxic. If we are so healed
then our actions should be different. we
should be showing up differently and
you're not. You are consistently showing
up in a way that makes you
unrecognizable to those of us that have
loved you, respected you, and defended
you. A madam for all fakey fufu boo last
names a [ __ ] fool Cheyenne Bryant.
You got on that show and defended that
causing children pain by putting your
hands on them. Physical violence hitting
them, popping them is not abuse, but
instead discipline. I want to know when
you get popped in the mouth, you know,
not because people are abusing you, but
because they love you and they have to
show you that you were wrong. So they're
disciplining you. How do you as an adult
regulate? Or have you not been popped in
the mouth as an adult?
>> You don't regulate. You tell to shut the
[ __ ] up. You don't regulate. You tell, a
grown ass man who was supposed to be
wrapping up the show, to shut the [ __ ]
up when he's talking to you.
>> Cuz I think we [clears throat] might
need to put this one to test in trial.
You don't know the difference between
gentle parenting and permissive
parenting. If gentle parents are raising
gentle children, they're gentle because
they understand the boundaries that you
say gentle parenting and gentle children
don't [ __ ] have. If you tell a child
gentle, gentle with the puppy, they know
to slow down and soften their movements
and be more gentle because the parents
have explained if you're too rough with
the dog, dog may bite your ass. So the
children learn a boundary. So when you
have gentle adults, when you have gentle
people that parent their kids, it's
because they understand there is a
certain boundary that cannot be crossed
when trying to discipline, when trying
to educate for the sake of keeping that
child open and making sure that
everybody stays emotionally regulated.
>> And then here you guys, I think that's
the point. The reason why Cheyenne
Bryant doesn't believe in gentle
parenting because she doesn't even know
how to gentle parent herself. The fact
that an unlicensed healed person has so
much deceit to someone who's lying about
being a doctor
is scary. I am scared for the doc squad.
The doc squad, right? Shout out to the
blue crew. I love y'all. I'm scared for
the doc squad because in the midst of
all this loving, fair, sometimes
passionate and scathing critique that is
a lot of times very valid and nuanced,
her response, Dr. Bryan's response. I'm
going to have to mute it cuz it has um
music playing. You guys, if you have not
heard Cardi B's song, Pretty and Petty
as [ __ ] uh I'll have to sing it for you
cuz I don't want to get a copyright
strike. But this was Dr. Bryant's
response to all of us.
The caption said, "Y'all still talking."
And under on top of the y'all still
talking, she posted this video. I'm
pretty and I'm petty as [ __ ] I'm gonna
sing it. I'm pretty and I'm petty as
[ __ ] I'm pretty and I'm petty as [ __ ]
And then she's making sure that we can
see how flat her stomach is. I'm pretty
and I'm petty as [ __ ] Yes, I'm pretty
and I'm petty as [ __ ] This is her
response.
This is doctoral
hard eye because I made it up. This is
doctoral candidate
uh the the president of Narnia ran ran
for mayor. Okay. She ran for mayor in
the never- ending story and almost won,
but let Karen Bass have it. Okay, this
is her response.
I'm pretty and I'm petty as [ __ ] Y'all
done talking?
You know what, Dr. Cheyenne Bryant?
Sorry, doctoral Cheyenne Bryant. You're
right. I am done talking. That concludes
our live, guys. I got to head to
Carlos's show. Blue Crew, if you meet me
over there, go to Carlos King's page.
Shot yourselves out. Let let me know
that you're in the room. I'm going to
grab a quick drink and then I'll see
y'all in 10 minutes over there. And I'm
traveling this week, but I will be
having a pre-taped video for y'all. I
may or may not have discovered the next
Danish deception. There's a Danish
Deception like video that I'm going to
be watching and posting sometime this
week for y'all. And I cannot wait to
hear your feedback because what the
[ __ ]
We thought ana was the end of it.
There's a whole new uh grifter in town.
Somebody said ew. I know, right? All
right. I love you guys. Uh, please make
sure you like the live and if you want
to have the comment during the replay
because you guys know I love it when you
guys comment during the replay. The
comment for those who made it to the
end, that's how I know you watched the
end of the video is you ain't got a lot
of kicking shy shy.
Okay, you ain't got a lot of kick and
shy shy. Okay, live for no [ __ ]
reason. All right, love you family. Bye.
Like the live. Don't forget to like the
live.